APURV HATWALNE

E-mail: apurv.hatwalne@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

To continue my career with an organization that will utilize my Management, supervision and administrative skills to benefit mutual growth and success, while continuously building my own library of knowledge and experience, as I advance in my professional career.

SUMMARY

I worked as a project manager at Oyo Hotels and Homes Pvt. Ltd, where in I took care of the live ongoing projects for property management aligned with Oyo. Prior to this, I have around 3 years of work experience as Senior Executive in HCL Technologies in the field of project/program management. My experience includes assignments in IT service delivery, pre-sales, market research, risk & compliance assessment, asset management and data analytics where my responsibilities were to coordinate with internal support verticals of the organization and the client, and eventually look after the operational quality and execution within the project and also at Regional Delivery Unit level. I have worked with well-known global conglomerates on multiple phases like procurement, vendor payment reviews, project budgeting, revenue & cost, and also profit improvement planning of the project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oyo Hotels & Homes Pvt. Ltd. Project Manager

Pune Oct 2019 – Jan 2020

Mobile: +91-7028841188

- Handling project for monthly signing of Oyo properties and tracking to make them live
- Working on financial reconciliation of churned property owners to winback for Oyo
- Coordinating with front end verticals of BD, Transformation and Operations for all Franchise properties and conduct regular internal meetings between verticals for better visibility and monitoring
- Working on recovery of pending payments of Oyo properties for revenue growth
- Organizing internal programs for monthly missions of the organization

HCL Technologies Senior Executive

Noida July 2016 – June 2019

- Revenue, Cost and Margin analysis by identifying various Cost parameters, end to end billing for the Project, Analysis of monthly/quarterly profit improvement plan (PIP)
- Analyzing customer requirement and handling pre-sales of licenses/asset procurement for clients including Sensata Technologies,
 Teradyne Inc., Univar Inc., Comcast and TRW Automotive
- Handled strategic initiative of productivity improvement and gained new business by publishing feasibility and productivity report at client level for the projects in the DU
- Successfully carried out Risk and Compliance audit at account level in & ensured SLA achievement in monthly tracking
- Reviewed customer contract, successfully carried risk assessments and gained new business from existing customers by publishing audit reports at client level
- Driving the PIP (profit improvement plan) so as to achieve the defined target in the assigned projects
- Regular Tracking of Service Level Agreement (SLA) achievements to ensure zero financial penalty
- Conducting monthly metrics and Quarterly Business Review with the customer
- Project SPOC for all the support functions (Admin ,HR, Quality , Transport) and resources in the project
- Successfully carrying out strategic initiatives of industrialization and productivity improvement for the whole RDU including 30 projects
- Gained new business through cross-functional training among the projects in the DU

Grand View Research INC. Management Trainee

Pune (HQ) May 2015 to June 2015

- Performing in-depth analysis on competitors in diversified markets which includes competitor overview, financial performance analysis, strategic analysis, portfolio assessment & mapping
- Market Intelligence: Performing market analysis including macroeconomic dynamics, market size, trends, and drivers
- Implementing research methodology and statistical models, PESTEL analysis, marketing estimates and forecasting for customer reports

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

- Ability to plan and execute client engagements end-to-end in a customer-centric manner and with minimal supervision
- Ability to identify sales opportunities while performing the audit engagements through understanding of the client's processes/requirements and data analysis
- Ability to confidently present data and have meaningful discussions at the Executive Leadership

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

Project/ Program management – Strategic initiatives

Financial metrics for project & DU

Internal audits/process audits

Risk and compliance

Asset management

Market research

SYSTEM SKILLS

Microsoft office suit – Word, Excel and PowerPoint

Certified in Knowledge management program by Deloitte

Trained in ITIL – V3 foundation program

MS-Excel and Basics of Macros/VBA

PERSONALITY TRAITS

Detail-Oriented

Quick Learner and good grasping power

Team Player

Multitasking and Time Management

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

- Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) in Marketing
 Balaji Institute of Modern Management, Pune 2014 2016
- Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science Engineering (CSE)
 Rajeev Gandhi Proudyogiki Vishwavidyalaya, Bhopal 2009 2013
- Senior Secondary Certificate Examination (SSCE) CBSE
 St. Joseph's Co-Ed School, Bhopal 2007 2008
- Higher Secondary Certificate Examination (HSCE) CBSE
 - St. Joseph's Co-Ed School, Bhopal 2005 2006

PERSONAL DETAILS

- Father's Name
 Mr. Vijay Hatwalne
- Mother's Name Mrs. Seema Hatwalne
- Date of Birth May 8, 1990
- Languages Known
 English, Hindi, Marathi
- Permanent City Bhopal, Madhya Pradesh
- Current CityPune, Maharashtra